Olga Holm: multimedia designer junior frontend developer



Goal of this CV

I am web-designer and web-developer (frontend specialisation).

Currently, I am looking for a full-time position in a company located in **Copenhagen** with a focus on **web and mobile development and design,** starting from July-September 2019.

I have 2 year experience in using HTML, CSS, SASS pre-processor, Bootstrap library, JavaScript, Angular framework, PHP and mySQL, as well as Wordpress CMS for study projects. I am very interested in UX/UI design.

Link to a projects portfolio www.komar.dk

Link to a student portfolio www.komar/study

Education

CPH Business Academy, Lyngby

Multimedia Design and frontend development (2017-2019), AP

Bachelor degree in International Business

Belarusian State Economic University, faculty of International Economic

Relations (1995-2000)

Languages

Danish - fluent, English - fluent, German - basic, Russian - native

Personal

Born in Belarus in 1978, live in Denmark since 2011. Optimistic, responsible, diligent and smart person. ESTP-A personality. I like to learn new things and enjoy interesting challenges in life. My hobbies are cars, meditation, yoga,

travelling, and reading. Married, no children.

Work experience

My previous work experience lays in business administration, marketing, advertising and project-management. 2 years ago I have decided to invest time and effort to pursue my dream to use my interest to technologies and learn to program.

Thus my future employee will get a motivated tech specialist with experience in business processes and project-management.

Portfolio link: www.komar.dk CV updated 15.07.2019

Work experience in details:

Visas and Legalisations handling officer

Consular services agency, Comet Consular Services A/S (www.cometconsular.com) Copenhagen, Denmark

September 2013 until now

Responsibilities:

- establish and maintain cooperation with embassies/consulates and other authorities
- handling visa applications and legalisation of documents through the embassies in Copenhagen
- giving update on ongoing cases to clients via email, telephone and in person
- keeping updated the company's information database on the daily basis
- daily accounting of expenses in connection with the document flow

Head of the office

Russian visa application center, Invisa Fiduciary Services Aps (<u>www.ifs-denmark.com</u>), Copenhagen,
Denmark

August 2012 - July 2013

Responsibilities:

- overall management of the office and its daily procedures
- establishing the procedures in connection with the applications for Russian visas
- contacting the Russian consulate on the daily basis
- personnel management
- financial and overall reporting

Head of the subsidiary with the overall responsibility for leading the department

Internet advertising sales-house, RG
Media (<u>www.rgmedia.by</u>,
<u>www.redgraphic.com</u>), Minsk,
Belarus

March 2009 - May 2010

Responsibilities:

- working out and adopting the yearly financial plan of the subsidiary
- negotiating and establishing partnerships with partners
- setting up sales targets, creating price lists, discount grids and drafts of agreements with customers and partners
- reporting to the company's owner on turnover statements and results
- hiring and managing of personnel, freelancers and maintenance assistants

Country sales representative (Russia, Ukraine, Belarus)

Spanish cheese manufacturers association Quorum International

Responsibilities

- establishing partnership with food importers and distributors of the diary products
- representing the association at exhibitions and Spanish trade chamber events

Portfolio link: www.komar.dk CV updated 15.07.2019

(www.quoruminter.com), Moscow, Russia

March 2007 - December 2008

- translating and creating promotional materials and presentations
- assisting in negotiations between the association customers in Russia, Ukraine and Belarus

Head of advertising and PR division

International holding of transport and logistic companies AsstrA Associated Traffic AG (www.asstra.com), Moscow, Russia / Minsk, Belarus April 2002 - March 2007

Responsibilities

- creating, adopting and controlling of advertising and PR plans for overall activity on company's markets (Russia, Ukraine, Belarus, Lithuania, Poland, Germany, Italy, Switzerland, Kazakhstan, China)
- managing the division of advertising and PR (3 people) and coordinating the network of the sales managers (8 people) in local offices responsible for local marketing
- establishing and developing partnerships with subcontractors in all the markets
- participating in marketing strategy development and ISO 9001:2000 certification

Business development assistant

financial information agency Ecopress Ltd.(www.ecopress.by), Minsk, Belarus

February 2001 - March 2002

Responsibilities

- project management and promotion of the Belarusian news and search portal
- translation of news and documents for clients
- creating and running the new division for headhunting services within the company's activities - from business plan to sales

Other activities

From January 2009 til present: organizer and tour-leader of the yearly 3-week tour on the Trans-Siberian railroad for about 300 international participants with cultural and tourist program in the major Russian cities (www.lovingrussia.org).

Portfolio link: www.komar.dk CV updated 15.07.2019